

Applicant for:

Android Developer (Java/Kotlin) ~ 2000\$

Dr.JOY 1 March 2020

Trần Văn Thắng

Main interests: Android, iOS

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Trần Văn Thắng skipped the cover letter.

TRAN VAN THANG

Date of birth: Jul 16, 1992

Gender: Male

Phone: +84 961 615 755

Email: tranthangbk55@gmail.com

Address: 180 Nam Du, Hoang Mai, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Current Job: Android Developer at TLSoft No 71, Ngo Sy Lien, Dong Da, Ha Noi)

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/thang.tranvan.1607



EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

5+ years of software experience

Strong experiences in Android, Java/Kotlin

Good at Object Oriented Programming, Design pattern

Knowledgeable of image processing and database design

SQL lite, Realm, json, Rest Api...

Good at Algorithm

Experienced working in global company and big projects.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sep 2019 – Present	TLSoft Company No 71, Ngo Sy Lien, Van Mieu, Dong Da
January 2019 – Aug 2019	VCC: Viettel Construction Joint Stock Corporation No 6, Pham Van Bach, Yen Hoa, Cau Giay
June 2015 – December 2018	SVMC: Samsung Viet Nam Mobile Center No 1, Pham Van Bach, Yen Hoa, Cau Giay
May 2013 – May 2015	Join to Sansan Lab at university Smart tour project (Android) , The quality of water (HW)
EDUCATION	

EDUCATION

Oct 2010 - May 2015	Hanoi University of Science & Technology School of Electronics and Telecommunications
Oct 2007 - May 2010	Nhi Chieu High School, Kinh Mon, Hai Duong

SKILLS

OITIELO	
Objective	 To be a good staff Enduring well under intense pressure Good at presentation Ability to work independently or in group with enthusiasm and high responsibility Try to learning as much as possible and doing my best in order to accomplish my task. Develop my skill with development of company, I want to prove myselt.
Programming Language	 Java Programing - 4 years Android Programing - 4 years Kotlin - 1 year React Native - 2 months
Programing Skills	 Model View Presenter(MVP) Object oriented programming (OOP) Algorithm: Searching, Sorting Design Pattern: MVP, Singleton, Builder, Observer (Rx Java, Rx Android)
Android Skills	 Developer application Android Worked with Activity, Fragment, Service, Content Provide, Intent, Broadcast Receiver, Application, Shared Preference, Sqlite Knowledge of application lifecycle, activity lifecycle, fragment lifecycle ,context Knowledge of view basic and advance, material design, multiple screen. Used MVP, MVVM in Application. Database: sqlite, room, realm Network: rest api, json, firebase Protect source code application: proguard, android NDK User Android Architecture Components: livedata, view model, room, work manager
IDE – Tool	Platforms: Android studio, Eclipse, Github, Perforce,

CERTIFICATIONS

July	2017	TOEIC Certificate with is 550
Aug	2016	Advanced Samsung Certificate Technical (Algorithm)

PROJECT

1. MyFiles (Product app, Android)	 Possition: Member (Total 5 menbers) Program Language: Android Feature: Display all files: music, image, voice, folder And operation related to item: copy, move, Job: Take over from HQ, maintain and impliment some functions as: google driver, move file, get more space Applied model: All samsung models
 Voice Recorder (Product app, Android) May 2017 – present 	 Possition: Member (Total 9 members) Job: Take over from HQ, maintain and impliment some functions as: simple voice from setting and message app, move all item between others category Program Language: Android Applied model: All samsung models
3. ISTools (Java) Jan 2018 – May 2018	 Possition: Member (Total 6 members) Program Language: Java Feature: Aplugin for android studio Job: Push database, install/uninstall app, reset data of device via Android Studio Applied model: not yet
4. FamilyCare (Android) June 2016 – Dec 2017	 Possition: Member (Total 10 members) Program Language: Android Feature: Family Care is a parental control app that helps parent take care of their children's smartphone usage habits. Parent can restrict how much time a child should spend for one app (some essential apps like phone, sms, contact, settings cannot be restricted) Job: desisgn database, structure app, block app modul Applied model: A5, A7 Samsung
5. 600 essential vocabulary (Product App, Android)	 Possition: Main owner Program Language: Android Feature: App to help people study 600 essential vocabulary. Technologies: SQL database, animation, asyn task, Cursor loader, Cardview and Recycler view Others: Apply in store play

6. Bao net 24H (Product App, Android)

November 2018 - present

- Possition: Main Owner (Total: 2 members)
- Program Language: Android
- Feature: Read Newspaper in 24/24.
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end
- Technologies: retrofit , loadmore , shimmer effect, drawer navigation, tablayout , viewpager, asyn task, cardview and recyclerview...
- 7. All In One (Product App, Android)

November 2018 - present

- Possition: Main Owner (Total: 2 members)
- Program Language: Android
- Feature: Product of VCC
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end
- Technologies: Volley, MVVM, NDK android,QR code, Barcode...
- 8. All In One (Product App, Android)

November 2018 - present

- Possition: Main Owner (Total: 2 members)
- Program Language: Android
- Feature: Product of VCC
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end
- Technologies: Volley, MVVM, NDK android,QR code, Barcode...
- Quản lý tài sản (Product App, Android)

May 2019 - present

- Possition: Main Owner (Total: 1 members)
- Program Language: Android
- Feature: Product of VCC
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end
- Technologies: Volley, MVVM, NDK android...
- Xây lắp công trình (Product App, -Android)

May 2019 - present

Possition: Main Owner (Total: 1 members)

- Program Language: Android
- Feature: Product of VCC
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end
- Technologies: Volley, MVVM, NDK android...
- BaoViet Agency (Product App, -Android)

Sep 2019 - present

Possition: Main Owner (Total: 2members)

- Program Language: Android Koilin
- Feature: Product of BaoViet
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end

Technologies: AndroidX, Retrofit, Material Design, MVVM,

- Rxjava...
- BaoViet Office (Product App, -Android)

Sep 2019 - present

Possition: Main Owner (Total: 2 members)

- Program Language: Android Kotlin
- Feature: Product of BaoViet
- Job: structure app, design and implement all fuction from front- end
- Technologies: Retrofit, Material Design, MVVM, Rxjava...

INTERESTS

Football, Pes 3-4, Fifa Online, Readding books....